Guide to the Hunter R. Rawlings president emeritus papers, 2007-2017.
Rawlings, Hunter R. president emeritus papers
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Hunter R. Rawlings president emeritus papers, 2007-2017.
3-13-4219
Rawlings, Hunter R.
.6 cubic feet.
Reports, printed materials, other documents.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes subject files, event programs and other material pertaining to President Emeritus Rawlings' alumni, development, and administrative work with Cornell Universtiy.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
President, Cornell University, 1995-2003.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes subject files, event programs and other material pertaining to President Emeritus Rawlings' alumni, development, and administrative work with Cornell Universtiy.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Rawlings, Hunter R.; Cornell University -- Presidents.; Cornell University -- Administration.
Subjects:
Presidents.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of office of origin. Restriction reviews may take up to a month for completion.
RELATED MATERIALS
See also Hunter Ripley Rawlings papers, #3-13-2843.
CONTAINER LIST
- Rawlings Stewardship Letter, August 2006 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Beijing, July 24, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Shanghai All Alumni Reception, July 26, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Robert Richardson Reception, September 24, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Research Libraries Keynote, October 10, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Berg Foremost Benefactor, October 20, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Friedman Event, November 16, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Reunion: Classes 1958, 1963, 1968, June 5-8, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Cornell Commitment Dinner, September 6, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Altschuler Terrace Dedication, September 24, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Ray Williams Memorial Service, October 3, 2008 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- CBAA Dinner, June 5, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Wiswall Dedication, June 6, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Scholarship Dinner at Tolani's, September 15, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- H.R. Friedman Scholarship Reception, December 8, 2009 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Cardso Introduction (Bartels Lecture), April 7, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Alexander Scholarship Reception, August 29, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Singapore/India, September 2010 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Henry Paulson Faculty Lunch, November 11, 2010 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- F. Robinson Retirement, March 8, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Rosen Entrepreneur of the Year, April 14, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Zakaria Intro (Bartels Lecture), April 25, 2011 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Faculty / Curriculum Initiative, 2016-2017 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Weiss Presidential Award 1, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Weiss Presidential Award 2, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Weiss Presidential Award 3, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Weiss Provost's Teaching Award, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Weiss Jr. Presidential Award, 2016 (Box 2, Folder 5)